MD. MAZBAUR RASHID

STUDENT, DAFFODIL INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY



CONTACT ME AT

- Mirzapur, Tangail
- +8801796228391
- mazbaur15-2837@diu.edu.bd
- https://cutt.ly/JWxEBcz
- in @mazbaurrashid

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Programming
- •••• Coding
- •••• Research
- •••• Leadership
- •••• Web development
- •••• Software Testing
- •••• Graphics
- •••• Wordpress
- •••• Object-Oriented Design

PERSONAL PROFILE

A Virtual Assistant with 2 years experience in various tasks. A tech savvy and problem solver that you can rely on. Have experience of working as a Student Prefect, Research, Developing Web & Web Applications and Managing Databases.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Business Development Manager

IT Company (Webio) | 2021 - Present

- Maintained client works.
- Managed company web and content

Associate Software Engineer

Social Media Page & Web (Consumers Complaint Center) | 2020 - Present

- Post creation and regular update of websites (Code, Design, Posts, Video)
- Managing content (back-end+front-end) in web.

Software Engineer

Online News Portal (Voktakantho)| 2020 - Present

- Maintained positive work ethic and commitment to providing excellent service.
- Managing content (back-end+front-end) in web.
- Managing heavy load administrative tasks with accuracy.

Content Creator

Zadur Kouta | 2020 - 2021

- Making video content and graphic designing.
- Prepared detailed reports and contents

LANGUAGE







LANGUAGE

PROGRAMMING

•••• C

•••• C++

•••• Python

•••• Java

SCRIPTING

•••• PHP

•••• HTML, CSS

Javascript

FRAMEWORKS

•••• React

••• Bootstrap

DATABASE

•••• SQL

EDUCATION HISTORY

Daffodil International University
Computer Science Engineering | 2019 - Studying

- Study and Extra Curriculur Activities
- Made Contents that published on DIU Youtube and Facebook page
- CGPA: 3.98 out of 4.00

Sristy College of Tangail Higher Secondary Certificate | 2018

- President at SCT Science Club
- Program Organizer
- GPA: 4.72 out of 5.00

Mirzapur S.K. Pilot Model High School Secondary School Certificate | 2016

- Team leader
- Teacher Assistant
- GPA: 5.00 out of 5.00

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

Contest Award

Take-Off Programming Contest

- Rank 3rd
- Position 5th

Battle of mind 2.0

- Got a chance to participate on BOM
- Organised by Daffodil International University

Appreciation Award

DIU Voluntary Service Club

- · Creative designing
- Video editing

Medal

Code Hunt

• Position - 1st

Best Trainer award

Use of Canva through Mobile Devices

- Took 2 classes
- 80 students enrolled on that course
- Paid course

King of fighter

Given by Voktakantho for best in

- Web management
- · Creative design

SOFTWARE

MS OFFICE

- MS Word
- •••• MS Powerpoint
- •••• MS Excel

GOOGLE

- •••• Docs (Word)
- •••• Slide (Powerpoint)
- •••• Sheet (Excel)
- •••• Google Forms

ADOBE

- •••• Photoshop
- •••• Illustrator
- •••• Premiere Pro
- •••• After Effetcs

OTHERS

- •••• Filmora (For Video Editing)
- •••• Canva
- •••• Anydesk

TEACHING EXPERIENCES

- Prefect of Object Oriented Programming LAB (Java, 2 semesters)
- · Prefect of Algorithms LAB
- Prefect of Object Oriented Programming II LAB (Python, 1 semester)
- Prefect of Computer Networks LAB

PROBLEM SOLVING EXPERIENCES

Have 300+ solving history in following platforms

- Codeforces
- Hackerrank
- URI Online Judge

CLUB EXPERIENCES

Creative Designer

DIU Voluntary Service Club | 2020 - Present

- Making video content and graphic designing.
- Making banner, Posts, Content, Videos, Google forms etc

LEADERSHIP CAPABILITIES

Have a lot of leadership experience. In each semester I have lead my team in every project and I have received very good feedback from the teachers and also got very good grades in all those courses.

OTHER CAPABILITIES

- · Can handle Domain & Hosting.
- Interact with Cpanel very well.
- Google Adsense handling.
- Wordpress admin panel and Plugins.
- Facebook Marketing & Facebook Business Suit.
- · Content making & writing.
- Facebook page handling with boosting.